<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?>
<modDesc descVersion="80">
  <author>aaw3k</author>
  <version>1.1.1.0</version>

  <title>
    <en>Mouse Steering</en>
    <de>Maussteuerung</de>
    <fr>Contrôle À La Souris</fr>
    <pl>Sterowanie Myszą</pl>
  </title>

  <description>
    <en><![CDATA[Thanks to this modification, you gain precise control over the vehicle's wheels using your mouse, allowing for realistic steering.

Changelog 1.1.1.0
- Added localization TR
- Improved steering input method for mouse steering
- Improved motor start warning logic for vehicle

Changelog 1.1.0.0
- Added localization IT
- Added support for multiplayer
- Added synchronization of vehicle wheel steering
- Added logic considering engine status
- Added information when wheels cannot be turned
- Added option to open keyboard control settings from the control menu
- Improved vehicle dialog layout for longer text
- Fixed camera rotation for worker and passenger
- Fixed incorrect text formatting in the mouse control menu slider

For more information or to report a bug, please visit <a href="https://github.com/modnext/mouseSteering">GitHub</a>.]]></en>
    <de><![CDATA[Dank dieser Modifikation erhältst du präzise Kontrolle über die Fahrzeugräder mit deiner Maus, was eine realistische Lenkung ermöglicht.

Änderungsprotokoll 1.1.1.0
- Lokalisierung TR hinzugefügt
- Verbesserte Eingabemethode für Maussteuerung
- Verbesserte Motorstart-Warnlogik für Fahrzeuge

Änderungsprotokoll 1.1.0.0
- Italienische Lokalisierung hinzugefügt
- Multiplayer-Unterstützung hinzugefügt
- Synchronisierung der Lenkung der Fahrzeugräder hinzugefügt
- Logik hinzugefügt, die den Motorstatus berücksichtigt
- Information hinzugefügt, wenn die Räder nicht gedreht werden können
- Option hinzugefügt, die Tastatursteuerungseinstellungen aus dem Steuerungsmenü zu öffnen
- Fahrzeugdialoglayout für längere Texte verbessert
- Kameradrehung für Arbeiter und Passagier behoben
- Falsche Textformatierung im Maussteuerungsmenü-Schieberegler behoben

Für weitere Informationen oder um einen Fehler zu melden, besuche bitte die <a href="https://github.com/modnext/mouseSteering">GitHub</a>.]]></de>
    <fr><![CDATA[Grâce à cette modification, vous obtenez un contrôle précis des roues du véhicule à l'aide de votre souris, permettant une conduite réaliste.

Journal des modifications 1.1.1.0
- Ajout de la localisation TR
- Amélioration de la méthode d'entrée de direction pour la commande à la souris
- Amélioration de la logique d'avertissement de démarrage du moteur pour le véhicule

Journal des modifications 1.1.0.0
- Ajout de la localisation IT
- Ajout du support multijoueur
- Ajout de la synchronisation de la direction des roues du véhicule
- Ajout de la logique tenant compte de l'état du moteur
- Ajout d'une information lorsque les roues ne peuvent pas être tournées
- Ajout de l'option d'ouvrir les paramètres de contrôle du clavier depuis le menu de contrôle
- Amélioration de la disposition des dialogues des véhicules pour les textes plus longs
- Correction de la rotation de la caméra pour le travailleur et le passager
- Correction du formatage incorrect du texte dans le curseur du menu de contrôle de la souris


Pour plus d'informations ou pour signaler un bug, veuillez visiter la page <a href="https://github.com/modnext/mouseSteering">GitHub</a>.]]></fr>
    <pl><![CDATA[Dzięki tej modyfikacji zyskujesz precyzyjną kontrolę nad kołami pojazdu za pomocą myszy, co pozwala na realistyczne sterowanie.

Dziennik zmian 1.1.1.0
- Dodano lokalizację TR
- Udoskonalono metodę sterowania dla sterowania myszą
- Poprawiono logikę ostrzegania o uruchomieniu silnika dla pojazdów

Dziennik zmian 1.1.0.0
- Dodano lokalizację IT
- Dodano wsparcie dla trybu wieloosobowego
- Dodano synchronizację skrętu kół pojazdu
- Dodano logikę uwzględniającą stan silnika
- Dodano informację, gdy nie można skręcać kołami
- Dodano opcję otwierania ustawień sterowania klawiaturą z menu sterowania
- Poprawiono układ dialogów pojazdów dla dłuższego tekstu
- Naprawiono obrót kamery dla pracownika i pasażera
- Naprawiono nieprawidłowe formatowanie tekstu w suwaku menu sterowania myszą

Aby uzyskać więcej informacji lub zgłosić błąd, odwiedź stronę <a href="https://github.com/modnext/mouseSteering">GitHub</a>.]]></pl>
  </description>

  <l10n filenamePrefix="l10n/locale"/>

  <iconFilename>icon_mouseSteering.dds</iconFilename>
  <multiplayer supported="true" />

  <extraSourceFiles>
    <sourceFile filename="src/main.lua" />
  </extraSourceFiles>

  <specializations>
    <specialization name="mouseSteeringVehicle" className="MouseSteeringVehicle" filename="src/specializations/vehicles/MouseSteeringVehicle.lua"/>
  </specializations>

  <actions>
    <action name="MS_TOGGLE" category="VEHICLE" axisType="HALF"/>
    <action name="MS_SAVE" category="VEHICLE" axisType="HALF"/>
    <action name="MS_PAUSE" category="VEHICLE" axisType="HALF"/>
    <action name="MS_SHOW_MENU" category="VEHICLE" axisType="HALF"/>
  </actions>

  <inputBinding>
    <actionBinding action="MS_TOGGLE">
      <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lctrl KEY_space"/>
    </actionBinding>
    <actionBinding action="MS_SAVE">
      <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lctrl KEY_period"/>
    </actionBinding>
    <actionBinding action="MS_PAUSE">
      <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lalt"/>
    </actionBinding>
    <actionBinding action="MS_SHOW_MENU">
      <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lctrl KEY_slash"/>
    </actionBinding>
  </inputBinding>
</modDesc>
