<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?>
<modDesc descVersion="106">
  <author>aaw3k</author>
  <version>1.3.1.0</version>

  <title>
    <en>Mouse Steering</en>
    <de>Maussteuerung</de>
    <fr>Contrôle À La Souris</fr>
    <pl>Sterowanie Myszką</pl>
    <ru>Управление Мышью</ru>
  </title>

  <description>
    <en><![CDATA[Steer your vehicles with the mouse for a more natural and fluid driving experience. Easily customize sensitivity, linearity, and dead zones via the settings button in the general settings menu. Features include a clear HUD indicator, speed-adaptive steering for better precision at high speeds, and an automatic camera-follow system.

Hotkeys:
- Press Left Ctrl + . to toggle Mouse Steering.
- Press Left Ctrl + , to toggle Camera Follow Steering.
- Press Left Ctrl + SPACE to center camera or look back (double-click).
- Hold Left Alt key to rotate camera with mouse.
- Press Left Ctrl + / to set steering as default for the current vehicle (toggle).
- Use Mouse Wheel to adjust vehicle speed (when active).

Changelog Version 1.2.x:
- Migrated to FS25 and reworked codebase
- Improved persistence and per-vehicle toggles
- Fixed error with fishing boats

Changelog Version 1.3.0.0:
- Added camera rotation and centering
- Disabled locomotives

Changelog Version 1.3.1.0:
- Improved camera orientation and centering
- Added smooth speed control via mouse wheel
- Added camera look-back (double-click)
- Added small optimization improvements

For more information or to report a bug, please visit GitHub (modnext/mouseSteering).]]></en>
    <de><![CDATA[Lenken Sie Ihre Fahrzeuge mit der Maus für ein natürlicheres und flüssigeres Fahrgefühl. Passen Sie Empfindlichkeit, Linearität und Totzonen ganz einfach über die Schaltfläche in den allgemeinen Einstellungen an. Zu den Funktionen gehören eine übersichtliche HUD-Anzeige, eine geschwindigkeitsabhängige Lenkung für mehr Präzision bei hohem Tempo und eine automatische Kamera-Folgefunktion.

Tastenkombinationen:
- Drücken Sie Linke Strg + . , um die Maussteuerung umzuschalten.
- Drücken Sie Linke Strg + , , um die Kamera-Lenkungsfolge umzuschalten.
- Drücken Sie Linke Strg + LEER, um die Kamera zu zentrieren oder zurückzublicken (Doppelklick).
- Halten Sie die Taste Linke Alt gedrückt, um die Kamera mit der Maus zu drehen.
- Drücken Sie Linke Strg + / , um die Steuerung für das aktuelle Fahrzeug als Standard festzulegen (umschalten).
- Verwenden Sie das Mausrad, um die Fahrzeuggeschwindigkeit anzupassen (wenn aktiv).

Änderungsprotokoll Version 1.2.x:
- Migration zu FS25 und Codebasis überarbeitet
- Sitzungsbeständigkeit und Umschalten pro Fahrzeug verbessert
- Fehler mit Fischerbooten behoben

Änderungsprotokoll Version 1.3.0.0:
- Kamerarotation und Zentrierung hinzugefügt
- Lokomotiven deaktiviert

Änderungsprotokoll Version 1.3.1.0:
- Verbesserte Kameraorientierung und Zentrierung
- Hinzugefügte Geschwindigkeitsregelung via Mausrad
- Hinzugefügter Kamerarückblick (Doppelklick)
- Hinzugefügte kleine Optimierungsverbesserungen

Für weitere Informationen oder um einen Fehler zu melden, besuchen Sie bitte GitHub (modnext/mouseSteering).]]></de>
    <fr><![CDATA[Dirigez vos véhicules à la souris pour une expérience de conduite plus naturelle et plus fluide. Personnalisez facilement la sensibilité, la linéarité et les zones mortes via le bouton dans les paramètres généraux du jeu. Les fonctionnalités incluent un indicateur HUD clair, une direction progressive pour plus de précision à haute vitesse et un système de suivi automatique de la caméra.

Raccourcis clavier:
- Appuyez sur Ctrl Gauche + . pour activer/désactiver la direction à la souris.
- Appuyez sur Ctrl Gauche + , pour activer/désactiver le suivi de la caméra.
- Appuyez sur Ctrl Gauche + ESPACE pour centrer la caméra ou regarder en arrière (double-clic).
- Maintenez la touche Alt Gauche enfoncée pour faire pivoter la caméra à la souris.
- Appuyez sur Ctrl Gauche + / pour définir la direction par défaut pour le véhicule actuel (basculer).
- Utilisez la molette de la souris pour ajuster la vitesse du véhicule (si actif).

Journal des modifications version 1.2.x:
- Migration vers FS25 et refonte du code
- Amélioration de la persistance de la session par véhicule
- Correction d'un bug avec les bateaux de pêche

Journal des modifications version 1.3.0.0:
- Ajout de la rotation et du centrage de la caméra
- Désactivation des locomotives

Journal des modifications version 1.3.1.0:
- Amélioration de l'orientation et du centrage de la caméra
- Ajout du contrôle fluide de la vitesse via la molette
- Ajout de la vue arrière (double-clic)
- Ajout de petites améliorations d'optimisation

Pour plus d'informations ou pour signaler un bug, veuillez visiter GitHub (modnext/mouseSteering).]]></fr>
    <pl><![CDATA[Steruj pojazdami za pomocą myszki, co sprawia, że jazda jest znacznie bardziej płynna i naturalna. Dostosuj czułość, liniowość i martwe strefy za pomocą przycisku w menu ustawień ogólnych. Funkcje obejmują czytelny wskaźnik HUD, system progresywnego skrętu dla lepszej precyzji przy dużych prędkościach oraz automatyczne śledzenie kierownicy przez kamerę.

Skróty klawiszowe:
- Naciśnij Lewy Ctrl + . , aby włączyć/wyłączyć sterowanie myszą.
- Naciśnij Lewy Ctrl + , , aby włączyć/wyłączyć śledzenie skrętu przez kamerę.
- Naciśnij Lewy Ctrl + SPACJA, aby wycentrować kamerę lub spojrzeć w tył (dwuklik).
- Przytrzymaj klawisz Lewy Alt, aby obracać kamerę myszą.
- Naciśnij Lewy Ctrl + / , aby ustawić sterowanie jako domyślne dla obecnego pojazdu (włącza/wyłącza).
- Użyj rolki myszy, aby dostosować prędkość pojazdu (gdy włączone).

Lista zmian w wersji 1.2.x:
- Migracja do FS25 i przebudowa kodu
- Poprawa trwałości stanu i przełączanie per pojazd
- Naprawiono błąd z łodziami rybackimi

Lista zmian w wersji 1.3.0.0:
- Dodano obrót i centrowanie kamery
- Wyłączono lokomotywy

Lista zmian w wersji 1.3.1.0:
- Poprawiono orientację i centrowanie kamery
- Dodano płynne sterowanie prędkością za pomocą rolki myszy
- Dodano możliwość patrzenia do tyłu (dwuklik)
- Dodano małe usprawnienia optymalizacyjne

Aby uzyskać więcej informacji lub zgłosić błąd, odwiedź GitHub (modnext/mouseSteering).]]></pl>
    <ru><![CDATA[Управляйте техникой с помощью мыши, что делает вождение гораздо более плавным и естественным. Настраивайте чувствительность, линейность и мертвые зоны через кнопку в общем меню настроек игры. Особенности включают удобный HUD-индикатор, прогрессивное рулевое управление для точности на высоких скоростях и систему автоматического следования камеры за рулем.

Горячие клавиши:
- Нажмите Левый Ctrl + . , чтобы включить/выключить управление мышью.
- Нажмите Левый Ctrl + , , чтобы включить/выключить следование камеры за рулем.
- Нажмите Левый Ctrl + ПРОБЕЛ, чтобы центрировать камеру или посмотреть назад (двойной щелчок).
- Удерживайте клавишу Левый Alt, чтобы вращать камеру мышью.
- Нажмите Левый Ctrl + / , чтобы установить управление по умолчанию для текущего транспорта (вкл/выкл).
- Используйте колесико мыши для регулировки скорости транспорта (когда активно).

Журнал изменений версии 1.2.x:
- Переход на FS25 и доработка кода
- Улучшено сохранение состояния и переключение для каждого ТС
- Исправлена ошибка с рыболовными лодками

Журнал изменений версии 1.3.0.0:
- Добавлено вращение и центрирование камеры
- Отключены локомотивы

Журнал изменений версии 1.3.1.0:
- Улучшена ориентация и центрирование камеры
- Добавлено плавное управление скоростью с помощью колесика мыши
- Добавлен обзор назад (двойной щелчок)
- Добавлены небольшие улучшения оптимизации

Для получения дополнительной информации или сообщения об ошибке посетите GitHub (modnext/mouseSteering).]]></ru>
  </description>

  <l10n filenamePrefix="l10n/l10n"/>

  <iconFilename>icon_mouseSteering.dds</iconFilename>
  <multiplayer supported="true" />

  <extraSourceFiles>
    <sourceFile filename="src/main.lua" />
  </extraSourceFiles>

  <specializations>
    <specialization name="mouseSteeringVehicle" className="MouseSteeringVehicle" filename="src/specializations/MouseSteeringVehicle.lua"/>
    <specialization name="mouseSteeringSpeedControl" className="MouseSteeringSpeedControl" filename="src/specializations/MouseSteeringSpeedControl.lua"/>
  </specializations>

  <actions>
    <action name="TOGGLE_MOUSE_STEERING_CONTROL" category="VEHICLE" axisType="HALF" displayCategory="VEHICLE_MOUSE_STEERING"/>
    <action name="TOGGLE_MOUSE_STEERING_SAVE_DELETE_VEHICLE" category="VEHICLE" axisType="HALF" displayCategory="VEHICLE_MOUSE_STEERING"/>
    <action name="TOGGLE_MOUSE_STEERING_ROTATE_CAMERA" category="VEHICLE" axisType="HALF" displayCategory="VEHICLE_MOUSE_STEERING"/>
    <action name="TOGGLE_MOUSE_STEERING_CAMERA_FOLLOW" category="VEHICLE" axisType="HALF" displayCategory="VEHICLE_MOUSE_STEERING"/>
    <action name="TOGGLE_MOUSE_STEERING_CENTER_CAMERA" category="VEHICLE" axisType="HALF" displayCategory="VEHICLE_MOUSE_STEERING"/>
  </actions>

  <inputBinding>
    <actionBinding action="TOGGLE_MOUSE_STEERING_CONTROL">
      <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lctrl KEY_period"/>
    </actionBinding>
    <actionBinding action="TOGGLE_MOUSE_STEERING_SAVE_DELETE_VEHICLE">
      <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lctrl KEY_slash"/>
    </actionBinding>
    <actionBinding action="TOGGLE_MOUSE_STEERING_ROTATE_CAMERA">
      <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lalt"/>
    </actionBinding>
    <actionBinding action="TOGGLE_MOUSE_STEERING_CAMERA_FOLLOW">
      <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lctrl KEY_comma"/>
    </actionBinding>
    <actionBinding action="TOGGLE_MOUSE_STEERING_CENTER_CAMERA">
      <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lctrl KEY_space"/>
    </actionBinding>
  </inputBinding>
</modDesc>
